{
    "subject": "resource/1,3,5-Triazine",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "1,3,5-Triazine",
    "human_readable": "The label of 1,3,5-Triazine is 1,3,5-Triazine.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9846941232681274,
            "question": "What is the label of 1,3,5-Triazine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9293059706687927,
            "question": "Are there any isomers of 1,3,5-Triazine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.918850302696228,
            "question": "Is '1,3,5-Triazine' a chemical compound?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9134824275970459,
            "question": "Can you name any common uses for 1,3,5-Triazine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8903170228004456,
            "question": "Where might you find information about the synthesis of 1,3,5-Triazine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8843303322792053,
            "question": "What is the chemical formula for 1,3,5-Triazine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8734875321388245,
            "question": "How does the structure of 1,3,5-Triazine affect its properties?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.858773946762085,
            "question": "What type of ring structure does 1,3,5-Triazine have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7967519760131836,
            "question": "What other chemical compounds share structural similarities with 1,3,5-Triazine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7287759780883789,
            "question": "How many nitrogen atoms are present in a 1,3,5-Triazine molecule?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of 1,3,5-Triazine is 1,3,5-Triazine.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8022_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other chemical compounds share structural similarities with 1,3,5-Triazine?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8022_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of ring structure does 1,3,5-Triazine have?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8022_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the structure of 1,3,5-Triazine affect its properties?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8022_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8022_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8022_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8022_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8022_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8022_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8022_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8022_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8022_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8022_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8022_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n``` \n\n\nThe document states:  \"1,3,5-Triazine IUPAC name 1,3,5-Triazine Other names sym-Triazine s-Triazine Cyanidine Hydrogen cyanide trimer\". \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The triple to be evaluated is \"The label of 1,3,5-Triazine is 1,3,5-Triazine.\" Given the context information:\n\n{'output': 'yes'} \n\nExplanation: The text mentions that \"1,3,5-triazine, also called s-triazine\", which indicates that the labels \"1,3,5-Triazine\" and \"s-triazine\" are indeed referring to the same chemical compound."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports the statement that the IUPAC name and other names for 1,3,5-triazine are indeed \"1,3,5-Triazine\" and include aliases such as \"s-Triazine\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}